One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Destroy Navy HQ!
Stay out of my line of fire.
Here he comes again!
Ice Ball!
– He froze Whitebeard!
– You did it!
Oh, my...
Looks like I can't freeze a quake man...
Ice...
Admiral Kuzan!
– He stabbed him with Haki!
– Is Aokiji dead?!
No! Don't be ridiculous.
Ice Block: Partisan!
Pops, get going!
I'm counting on you.
Diamond Jozu...
We're almost there!
I can see the execution platform!
We've just gotta break through in the confusion!
I won't let you!
You're all gonna die here!
A-Ace...
Oris Plaza
Straw Hat Luffy...
I, Momonga, stake my pride as a
Navy vice admiral on stopping you right here!
Vice admiral... So you're the same as Grandpa, huh?
Shave!
Moon Walk!
Gear...!
Secon...
Looks like you're out of energy!
Finger Pistol!
Garp. Consider your position!
You gotta have more than just courage...
Straw Hat Luffy,
without enough strength,
you can't save anyone, no matter how hard you try.
A-Ace...
– Kill Whitebeard!
– We won't let you!
Now will you please just disappear?
Ace's little brother!
Ace...
Oh. Whitebeard's command has been dulled...
To think that a man like you...
would let such reckless trash...
lead your attack.
We won't let you touch Pops!
Oh, how admirable...
There he is! It's Straw Hat-boy!
There he is, Jinbe!
Who's that?!
Where's that voice coming from?
Don't you see me?!
I'm Ivankov, dammit!
Up there!
What's with the size of his face?!
It's Ivankov, from the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy-kun!
Are you still alive, Straw Hat-boy?!
I'm... I'm...
not falling!
He fell!
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry...
What a noisy guy.
Iva-chan... Jinbe...
Let me go, old man!
I'm... I'm... Let me go!
He's done more than enough. Treat his wounds.
Yessir!
I don't need that! There's no time!
I've gotta go save him! Don't get in my way!
Ace is... Ace is...
Ace is...!
Ace is my only brother in the world!
I'll...
I'll definitely...
definitely...
save him!
Luffy-kun! Hey!
This is awful...
Please, Doctor!
Do whatever you can to keep him alive!
Luffy-kun! Luffy-kun!
Hang in there, Luffy-kun!
A bundle of spirit, who only knows how to talk big...
Young and clumsy...
I like fools like that...
Those with no regard for their lives, advance!
Here he comes! It's Whitebeard!
If we just let you run wild as you please...
the island won't be able to take it!
Then try to protect it!
Take care of Luffy-kun for me.
Jinbe, what about you?
I've chosen this as the place where I die!
We've gotta clear a path for Pops!
These are swordsmen as well... However...
Such pitiful weaklings!
Move!
Clear a path!
I must go to where Luffy is!
Do not interfere!
This is awful!
Boa Hancock has started attacking indiscriminately again!
Slave Arrow!
The corpses keep piling up!
I won't let you get in Pops' way!
I don't think I'm very tasty, actually...
I-I'm not done... Not yet...
Push them back!
That's...
The pirates' allies from the shore!
Sorry for the wait!
Yeah, we've been waiting for you!
Dammit! We let far too many of them get into the plaza!
Uncle will yell at me!
Under the circumstances,
some casualties will be inevitable,
but try to avoid hitting our own allies.
Pacifista!
Wait for me, Ace!
He's flying!
What are you doing?! Shoot him down!
Our guns won't work!
I don't care! Keep shooting!
Commander Marco!
Nobody told you to jump in on your own!
The Hero, Monkey D. Garp!
The legendary marine has finally made his move!
Vice Admiral Garp!
The vice admiral's in!
He's the best guardian we have!
Gramps...
Garp...
If you want to get past me, you'll have to kill me!
Dumb kids...